

Joseph H White UX Designer | Chicago IL

Bio

A Chicago-based designer coming from a varied user experience background of writing, performance, education, and hospitality.

Skillset

Visual Design
UX Design
User Research & Testing
Information Architecture
User Stories & Personas
Wireframing & Prototyping
Presenting and Demonstrating

Tools

Figma, Sketch, Whimsical, InVision, Illustrator, HTML & CSS, GitHub

Education

Bloc

User Experience Design Program

KD College

Actors Conservatory Program
Associates of Acting Performance

Find Me



312-219-6906



Joseph@placeholder.com



https://github.com/jhwwhite



Recent Projects

Production

Production is a cloud-based production managment application for writers, producers and all manner of magic makers

View Project

BusyBus

BusyBus is a bus tracking app that takes the guess work out of public transit

View Project

Other Experience

MIM Creatives 2017- Present

Meet Cute -Creator/ Head-Writer/ Director

A 10 episode audio-sitcom about two
groups of podcasters

Gear Up - Writer Short film

New Millennium Theater Co. 2011 - 2016 Marketing Director

Developed and maintain a process to advertise and market all productions

Worked with copywriters and graphic designers to manage the creation and distribution of all marketing collateral.

Chicago Public Schools 2009 - 2014 Recess Coordinator & Glee Club instructor

Created and maintained a structured recess for Pre-K-8th grade.

Glee Club instructor (4th - 8th grade): Musical director for children's choir